I'm here with MKBHD and we're going to
try to steal $10,000 from his locked
iPhone.
Really hope it doesn't work. Really hope
it doesn't work. I'm going to get you to
put that phone down on top of this
device.
>> It's just a regular payment terminal.
Nothing nothing weird about that.
>> Careful. [music]
Careful with that. Careful. Careful.
That's a lot of zeros. Careful with
that. Oh my god. Okay.
>> Do you do you even think it's possible
first firstly? $10,000?
>> I don't know if Apple [music] Pay will
let you do that.
>> Let's see it. Let's see if it works. I
feel like I'm a bit of a magician but
I'm like I wish
>> It hasn't changed anything, right?
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> It's it's still locked. It's locked.
Nothing else.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. We're going to start the script
again.
>> What just happened on my phone?
Approve Whoa. Whoa.